

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Nationality: Indian

Email: SHIPRA001@e.ntu.edu.sq

Mobile: (+65) 8359 1704

LANGUAGES

English (Business) Hindi (Native) Gujarati (Basic)

SUMMARY

The field of investment research and management is what drives Shipra in life. She has consistently demonstrated a strong zeal to work in the field of finding the best investment opportunities and seeks to leverage her experiences in an investment research/management role.

She is an experienced finance professional and qualified Chartered Accountant from India with 7+ years of working knowledge in the fields of Equity Research, Bank Audits, preparation of accounting statements and Indian taxation. She has extensive exposure in the analysis of financial and nonfinancial data. Due to her superior performance, Shipra was assigned the task of team management.

Shipra has been associated with two NGOs, Adhiyagya and Children International Organisation catering to children empowerment.

EDUCATION 2016-2017 (expected)

Master of Business Administration

Nanyang Technological University Nanyang Business School, Singapore

2007-2011

Chartered Accountancy

Institute Of Chartered Accountants Of India, Delhi, India

2007-2010

Bachelor Of Commerce (Hons.)

Delhi University

Kamala Nehru College, Delhi, India

LinkedIn:

www.linkedin.com/in/shiprashrimali

SHRIMALI, Shipra

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Evalueserve, India (Morgan Stanley)

Equity Research, Senior Research Associate

Jul 2015-May 2016

- Earned revenue of US\$5 million for Evalueserve while working with the sell-side Equity Research team of Morgan Stanley on company and industry specific analysis.
- Covered large-cap companies having market capitalization of more than US\$1.5 billion while tracking different sectors
 Retail, Telecom, Real Estate Development, Aviation and Auto.
- Assisted in handling client requests, which generated high revenues for Morgan Stanley.
- Worked on financial modeling and various relative valuations techniques and other multiples. Prepared earnings
 note, sector and thematic reports, and assisted clients to generate industry and stock specific insights and carried
 out comparative analysis of sectors through various metrics. Earned appreciation for the work performed.
- Collected financial data by using research tools and databases like Reuters, Bloomberg, etc. and was involved in search and aggregation of daily news pertaining to companies under coverage. Streamlined many procedures for collection and update of data.
- Prepared marketing presentations from time to time to help analyst get more business.

Uninet Strategic Management Limited, India

Dec 2014-Jul 2015

Equity Research, Associate Vice President

- High-booked return of more than US\$50,000 from first time investments done on the basis of equity research of Indian mid-cap companies through analysis of financial statements, industry trends and future prospects.
- Consistently encouraged and held fortnightly information sharing sessions on investments.
- Designed and maintained an MIS for investment transactions.

Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd., India

Feb 2012-Nov 2014

Internal Auditor, Senior Manager

- Analysis of transactions with an approach to unearth fake customer accounts, money laundering, other suspicious
 transactions and practices, and ensured compliance to regulatory requirements. Highlighted very critical
 observations w.r.t. AML/Regulatory deviations to management, safeguarding the bank from financial and
 reputational risks and earned appreciation from First Tier Audit Committee Meeting:
 - Detected forgery by 5 branch employees of transactions worth US\$9 million and curtailed their actions.
 - Reported mal practices for catering to unreasonable demands of elite customers with a relationship value of US\$6 million. Generated revised manual to explicitly mention ways to meet demands of these customers.
 - Identified discrepancies in state level taxation policies. Devised and implemented new policies.
- Basis performance, post completion of first year, additional responsibility was assigned to lead own audit
 assignments as well as independently review audit assignments of other teams. Mentored and supervised 10
 colleagues. Also, approval was given to conduct discussions with Senior Management as an Audit lead, making
 me the youngest to get such an opportunity and responsibility.
- Created process, risk, and control inputs for Thomson Reuter's Accelus audit software which was successfully launched at an all India level.
- Conducted group discussions and interviews during the hiring process, and was part of the disciplinary committee.

Vijay Kalra & Co., India

Sep 2007-Mar 2011

Article Trainee

• Earned revenue of US\$ 40,000 from conducting concurrent and statutory audit assignments, and filing income tax returns of clients. Responsible for finalizing financial accounts of clients, individuals & corporate.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Professional Qualifications/ Projects -

Strategy Project for Canon Inc. Inkjet Printers	2016-17
Equity Valuation Report at Nanyang Business School	2016-17
Chartered Accountant, Institute Of Chartered Accountants Of India	2012
NSE Certified Market Professional – Level 1 Certification, India	2012

Awards & Recognitions -

Participant, Ben Graham Stock Picking Competition, Ivey Business School	2017
Co-Chair, Banking & Finance Club, Nanyang Business School	2016-17
Nanyang Women in Business Scholarship, Nanyang Business School	2016
Considered amongst the best performing employees in Internal Audit Department, Kotak	2012-2014
Stood Second in batch in B. Com (Hons.)	2010
Blue Blazer Holder and Five-year Consecutive Scholar, Delhi Public School, R.K. Puram, India	2002-2007

Interests -

Travelling, watching cinema, organising cultural events, tracking Indian stock market, community involvement through pro-bono services for different NGOs in India – volunteer in Adhiyagya and sponsor in Children International Org.